



 

   //Questions array

   let questions = [

    {

         number:1,

         question: "__ refers to communication by letters or emails exchanged",

         answer : "Correspondence",

         options : [

                          "Business communication",

                          "Public relation",

                          "Circular",

                          "Correspondence"

                        ]

    

    },

    {

         number:2,

         question: "All are forms of business correspondence except",

         answer : "Financial statement",

         options : [

                          "Business letter",

                          "Memorandum",

                          "Financial statement",

                          "Curriculum vitae"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:3,

         question: "Which of these is not a part of a business letter",

         answer : "Distribution list",

         options : [

                          "Name of the organisation",

                          "Distribution list",

                          "Postal address",

                          "Reference number"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:4,

         question: "letter writing, when the writer’s address is punctuated, it is referred to as ___ style",

         answer : "Close style",

         options : [

                          "Open style",

                          "Close style",

                          "Indented style",

                          "Block style"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:5,

         question: "Salutation in business letters comes after __",

         answer : "Recipient’s address",

         options : [

                          "Writer’s address",

                          "Recipient’s address",

                          "Heading",

                          "Date"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:6,

         question: "___ serves the purpose of the given in a nutshell what the letter is all about",

         answer : "First paragraph",

         options : [

                          "Subject matter",

                          "First paragraph",

                          "Letterhead",

                          "Title"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:7,

         question: "The first paragraph of a letter is ___ in function",

         answer : "Introductory",

         options : [

                          "Supporting",

                          "Leading",

                          "Introductory",

                          "Expository"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:8,

         question: "___ paragraph states the action required of the receiver",

         answer : "Concluding paragraph",

         options : [

                          "First paragraph",

                          "Second paragraph",

                          "Concluding paragraph",

                          "Middle paragraph"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:9,

         question: "___ is used to indicate that the same letter has been produced and made available for persons occupying several offices",

         answer : "Carbon copies",

         options : [

                          "Letter heading",

                          "Postal address",

                          "Enclosure",

                          "Carbon copies"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:10,

         question: "Where are extra documents attached to a letter written down",

         answer : "Enclosure",

         options : [

                          "Letter heading",

                          "Concluding paragraph",

                          "Enclosure",

                          "Carbon copies"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:11,

         question: "Memorandum is __ type of business correspondence",

         answer : "Internal correspondence",

         options : [

                          "Internal correspondence",

                          "External correspondence",

                          "Informal correspondence",

                          "None of the above"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:12,

         question: "Curriculum vitae is the Latin term meaning",

         answer : "Course of one's life",

         options : [

                          "Business information",

                          "Circle of life",

                          "Course of one's life",

                          "Personal statement"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:13,

         question: "An alternative term for the curriculum vitae is",

         answer : "Resume",

         options : [

                          "Memorandum",

                          "Resume",

                          "Business data",

                          "Circular"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:14,

         question: "At which section of the CV does a candidate need to state job or position he or she seeks to obtain",

         answer : "Objectives",

         options : [

                          "Publication",

                          "Personal data",

                          "Working experience",

                          "Objectives"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:15,

         question: "The shortest segments of the CV is ___",

         answer : "Extra curricular activities",

         options : [

                          "Additional skills",

                          "Extra curricular activities",

                          "Working experience",

                          "Objectives"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:16,

         question: "A person in a position to make reliable statements about a job candidate’s character, background and skills is called ____",

         answer : "Referees",

         options : [

                          "Guarantor",

                          "Referees",

                          "Beneficiaries",

                          "Job witness"  

                          ]

    

    }

     ];   